no slide 4:30
take the train I got the house to myself
I can finally rap alone back in Jersey
for the holidays I don't think I can
call it home started a company this year
this is straight in the valley thrown it
sucks
the only voice left at the party is
telling me that I should have known
you're 27 and never groans what these
things get to the top and you're less
alone all the pressures and stresses and
headaches you wake up feel great now you
stagnate and slip a shit when you're
over three minutes late
you still make fun of fat people in your
BMI is overweight I sort of feel like
I'm out of place a year goes by you look
around you down on the shitter
so down you can't be fucked if they call
you a switch a loser a little bitch who
didn't deliver by the type of guy who
comments and gets triggered if that's
the test that I didn't prepare looking
kind of stupid standing about underwear
should I rock Chris and be never scared
or leave therefore somewhere is this
feeling just here or is it everywhere
from the yes my chair shit-talking I
lost a girl I love this year
now I date myself like I'm Creek walking
I might sound like Drake
I told you in the old docks when we
lived in the closet like Harry Potter
never was much trust I just want to save
us in the future because never love
yourself and I never saw where you hold
on the train home he never doubted me we
made choices and try my best to drop out
buts getting loud on these words now is
there a place for people who actually
want to change the world don't just want
to make a buck and market it to boys and
girls and fill the earth with products
that are just out of their reach
themselves they're depressed and you can
sell them fucking lexapro
in conclusion society's the suckers and
if you still put in work you're a stupid
motherfucker